[
  {
    "question": "What is the capital of France?\n",
    "answer": "Paris"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the capital of Spain?\n",
    "answer": "Madrid"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the capital of Germany?\n",
    "answer": "Berlin"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the capital of Italy?\n",
    "answer": "Rome"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the capital of Poland?\n",
    "answer": "Warsaw"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the capital of Ukraine?\n",
    "answer": "Kiev"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the capital of Russia?\n",
    "answer": "Moscow"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the capital of Belarus?\n",
    "answer": "Minsk"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the capital of the United Kingdom?\n",
    "answer": "London"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the capital of the United States?\n",
    "answer": "Washington"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the capital of Canada?\n",
    "answer": "Ottawa"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the capital of Mexico?\n",
    "answer": "Mexico City"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the capital of Brazil?\n",
    "answer": "Brasilia"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the capital of Argentina?\n",
    "answer": "Buenos Aires"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the capital of Chile?\n",
    "answer": "Santiago"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the capital of Peru?\n",
    "answer": "Lima"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the capital of Colombia?\n",
    "answer": "Bogota"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the capital of Venezuela?\n",
    "answer": "Caracas"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the capital of Ecuador?\n",
    "answer": "Quito"
  }
]